Cade Meakin

1 Sheriffs Ride, Brownsfield Farm, Netherstowe Lane, Lichfield WS13 8EQ

cademeakin.github.io

cademeakin@gmail.com

Mobile: 07432 174491

Profile

I am an enterprising individual who has recently finished and completed my two year IT Diploma. I am currently a freelance web developer and employed as a part-time roofer and I am studying different computer languages and frameworks such as HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, Wordpress, PHP, MySQL, APIs, Python etc. using online courses. I am determined to continue my development and start a career as a UI & UX Designer and Front-End Web Developer. I also am passionate about Graphic Design.

Education

2017

CCA HTML Level 1

CCA CSS Level 1

CCA JavaScript Level 1

2015 - 2017

ICT Extended Diploma Level 3

South Staffordshire College, Tamworth

19 Units Including:

- Client-Side Web Design Created Web page
- Web Server Scripting Created multiple live server scripted functions
- Web Site Production Created complete and responsive web site
- Developing Computer Games Web application games
- Digital Graphics
- Animation
- Organisational Systems Security

Overall Grade: **DDD**

2010 - 2015

King Edwards VI High School

- OCR Level 2 Extended Certificate in IT User Skills
- OCR Level 2 NVQ Certificate in German

(10 GCSEs A-C Including Maths and English) Including:

- Mathematics B
- Further Mathematics C

Work Experience

January 2018 - March

Opus Digital Media

Contract work - Multiple Projects

- Individually designing and creating the UI/UX of client web sites
- Updating and maintaining client web sites

January 2018 - Current Freelance Web Design

Sites can be found on Portfolio

Designing, building and managing domain and hosting of sites.

June 2017

Age UK Tamworth

30+ hours

- Managed and maintained the web site of Age UK
- Uploaded documents and managed layout of the web page.

June 2014

Access Computers

2 Weeks

- IT Trouble Shooting, Repairs and Maintenance
- **Updated Databases**

2014 - Current

Armaclad Ltd.

Industrial Roofing and Cladding

- Part Time
- Commuting Across the Country
- Strict on site for 7:30 am

Extra Curricular Activities

Studying 7 Online Udemy Courses

To expand my knowledge in these programming languages and frameworks:

- HTML CSS JavaScript
- jQuery Bootstrap Wordpress PHP MySQL APIs Python
- Mobile Gaming Apps
- **NodeJS**
- **AngularJS**
- C#

Skateboarding, Snowboarding and Video Editing

Partaking of and filming of Skateboarding and Snowboarding

- It takes self discipline, self motivation and persistence to learn.
- Have already acquired skills and experience filming and editing videos since it has been a hobby of mine since early teenage years.

Basketball and Esports

Playing in a basketball team

Requires intense, fast paced team work.

Interests and Additional Information

Trained in Public Speaking

Since childhood I have been trained weekly in Public Speaking.

Own a full Drivers License and a Car

Gives me the ability to commute where necessary